TENZIN MIGMAR

WEB DEVELOPER / GRAPHIC DESIGNER

SUMMARY

A lifelong learner and a problem solver always enthusiastic to work on new ideas that improves the life around us. Working with creative people to teach each other and to solve bigger problem together as a team has been my greatest fun in my career.

KEY STRENGTHS

- JavaScript
- Ruby / Ruby on Rails
- React JS / React Native
- Node.js
- Python
- C/C++
- HTML5
- CSS Sass
- SQL / PostgreSQL
- phpMyAdminMySQL
- MongoDB
- jQuery
- Bootstrap
- Handlebars
- Git /Github
- Grunt / npm
- Adobe CC
- Wordpress
- Joomla
- Shopify

LANGUAGES

English: (Full knowledge) | Tibetan: (Full knowledge) Hindi: (Full knowledge) | French: (Beginner)

CONTACT



www.tenmediatech.com

github.com/tenmediatech

in linkedin.com/in/tenzin-migmar

EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer

Emory Tibet Science Initiative | 2015 - 2018 (Contract)

- Design more than 20 textbook and study material for ETSI science programs.
- Produced brochures and newsletter for international conference.

Web Designer

Science for Monks & Nuns | 2016 - 2018 (Contract)

- Created organization website (www.scienceformonks.org) and maintain website.
- Designed large panel for (My World My Responsibility) exhibition which is shown around the world in many cities.
- Produced digital and online material for the news, events and workshops.

Web & Graphic Designer

Web & Graphic Designer | 2014 - 2015

- Design graphics and website for company clients using CMS & Adobe CC.
- Creating and managing social media campaigns for client using Google Ads.

Multimedia Coordinator

Library of Tibetan Works & Archives | 2010 - 2013

- Designed organization web site (www.ltwa.net)
- Manage daily work for library multimedia office.
- Help multimedia staff in online and digital media publications.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Full Stack Web Development

General Assembly | 2018

- General Assembly's Web Development Immersive program is a 12-week career accelerator that focuses on full stack web development using the latest technologies. Following are some projects i did at GA.
- Book Repository Full stack single-page application book repository keep track of user books. Built with Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL, JavaScript, Handlebars, jQuery, AJAX, Bootstrap, and Sass.
- Browser Single Page Application Simple Tic Tac Toe browser game built with JavaScript,, jQuery, AJAX, Bootstrap, and Sass.
- Realtime Survey Express and Mongo dynamic realtime fist 2 five full stack survey application .

BCA / A Level

Department of Electronics and Accreditation of Computer Classes | 2004 - 2007

- Designed organization web site (www.ltwa.net)
- Manage daily work for library multimedia office.
- Help multimedia staff in online and digital media publications.